And that's why...
We need to hit a million channel
subscribers in six months!
If we don't...
Mayonaka Punch will be breaking up!
We're Breaking Up
That's way too slow!
It felt like time had stopped!
I've told you over and over that
timing is everything for captions!
Yes, Sensei!
Not to mention, this font
looks way too friendly!
We're Breaking Up
It's a bleak topic, so make sure
the text reflects that!
Do you understand?!
Yes! I'll do my best!
It really does look bleak, though...
Mayonaka Punch
48k subscribers
Good morning from the dead of night!
Subscribed
I need to figure something out.
What the...
Wh-What did they just say to each other?
How can these two be so...
Adorbs?
Fu?
Th-That was close.
But... it's okay, right?
My very first time can be with them.
[Prank] We Renovated Our Friend's Bathtub
Into a Baby Bath! [DIY]
260k views   1 day ago   ...more
Outside Kids
3.74m subscribers
Subscribe
Subscribed
3 Strategies to Hit 1 Million Subs in 6 Months!!
Just so you all understand...
A million subs in six months won't happen
without anything short of a miracle!
Even the famous TSUMA-shi
took three years to hit one million!
Th-Three years?!
So six months is definitely impossible, then!
Yes!
Not to mention that MayoPan
currently has just over 40k subs.
Normal methods won't get us anywhere.
Which is why I've devised
a three-step strategy.
3 Strategies to Hit 1 Million Subs in 6 Months!!
First, step one.
Uploading a slew of short videos every day!
We'll hook new people in
with shorts tuned to the algorithm!
Remember the Chu-Chu Girls' days?
Just like back then,
we'll play the numbers game!
Your Faves Are Adorbs, Hit That Subscribe
You were right!
A Nocturnal Girl Does
Radio Calisthenics 100k views
A Nocturnal Girl Trains
at a Sumo Stable 85k views
A Nocturnal Girl Saves a Farmer With
High-Speed Rice Planting 69k views
A Nocturnal Girl Drowns
in Pork Fat 91k views
Nocturnal Girls, Awaken Your Senses!
Blindfolded Musical Chairs... 97k views
Nocturnal Girls Find Paradise
in Their Backyard! 120k views
They're getting more views
than our usual videos!
I'm off to the shopping district
to brag about this!
Zoom-zoom!
Me, too!
Those old bats at the cashout counter
won't hear the end of it! Vroom, vroom!
Hold it!
Look at this.
Mayonaka Punch
50k subscribers
50k subscribers...
It feels like it's gone up a bit.
It's nothing considering all the views we got.
So time for step two of my strategy.
3 Strategies to Hit 1 Million Subs in 6 Months!!
Make them fall in love with
the channel and subscribe.
Once the shorts have gained traction,
we want to capitalize on that and have as many
people subscribe to the channel as we can.
But that's harder than you'd think!
Huh? Why's that?
You subscribe with the click of a button,
just like playing a video, right?
The click of a button!
Getting people to take that
one step is no mean feat.
For example, you can rack up hits
with clickbait thumbnails,
but if the video doesn't live up
to the hype, people won't subscribe.
In other words...
"I love this channel!"
Unless they think that,
they won't go so far as to subscribe!
Subscribe
Subscribed
So how do we win them over?
Well...
What kind of people do you like?
Masaki.
Other than me.
The man I fell in love with...
He always brought his lackeys as he
strutted down the streets at night.
But in private, he was a lonely man,
toppling cigarette butts like dominoes.
What Tokage just said...
She hit the nail on the head.
Where?!
In other words, to fall in love...
The keyword here is "unexpected."
So you mean like gap moe!
Yes.
We'll analyze the videos that
attract the most subscribers
and figure out the "gap"
that people want from us!
Huh?
What's up?
The one that gained us the most subs...
Makeover!!
Total Wardrobe Change
for a Filthy Slob
Makeover!!
Total Wardrobe Change
for a Filthy Slob
Tokage-san's wardrobe change?
This video was fun, wasn't it?
But it didn't really stand out that much.
Still, it's getting good numbers!
It's just a video of us drinking boba
and goofing around.
A ton of people left comments!
"I think I'll also grab some
boba tomorrow," it says!
Strawberry Milk
I think I'll also grab some boba tomorrow!
Rin
Gotta say... just adorbs <3
Satoru
I love hearing the three of you talk
We're seeing the birth of
Kikka the Influencer here!
I knew it.
The Dessert Trending Now
This video...
This Plain Jane
Can't Stop Talking About Fashion
And this one...
They've all led to more subscribers!
I've got it!
The audience from our shorts think MayoPan
is a group that only does weird stunts.
The gap that comes from that same MayoPan
being up-to-date on the latest trends—
that's what our new viewers are after!
The answer to step two is...
MayoPan x Trends
MayoPan combined with trends!
Eating the hot new gummies...
Using them as cooking ingredients...
With a good grasp on makeup and fashion!
All right!
Now we've completed step two!
Or so I thought...
Mayonaka Punch
51k subscribers
but it's not working at all.
Masaki...
Y-Yay?
Two.
Two?
From here on, we're doing
two new videos every day!
Two new videos?!
Uploading two videos every day.
This is how I'll bring us to the next phase!
We need to hit at least 150k subs soon,
or we'll never be able to get
to a million in six months!
That's why... I need to step up.
This is nothing.
I just won't sleep.
Just won't... sleep...
I don't... want to lose them again.
Oh, no! The editing!
Huh?
Get 1 mil!!
Good morning.
Did you do this?
Yep!
You fell asleep, so I took care of the lot!
Sorry for falling asleep.
Well? Aren't I amazing?
Just call me an editing master!
Master?
From now on, I can take over
editing whenever you want!
So when you need my help,
feel free to ask anytime!
After all, you and I make a great pair
that can't be separated!
Get real!
What?
Editing's not that easy.
You should be using way more
sound effects and BGMs.
Okay, let's dig in!
And you can trim a lot more
dead space between conversations!
Taste Test
Be more ruthless, and keep only the
parts that the viewers want to see!
Now I need to redo everything!
Snap!
Man, I swear!
Okay, let's dig in!
Taste Test
Oh!
Check out Fu drooling all over herself!
A-Am not!
She's hiding it!
Nuh-uh!
Ichiko, pat her down!
Yes, boss!
Stop it! I'll die of shame!
Prepare yourself!
Here I go!
So good!
Take this part...
and do this...
Okay, let's dig in!
So good!
This, this, this, and this can all go away!
H-Hey...
What?
F-Frankly speaking, there's no way
you can handle this many videos by yourself.
Right? So why don't we...
Not a friggin' chance!
You think I can have you
take over after seeing this?
Don't bother! I'll do it all myself!
What?!
Shoot three videos every day?
It's to save Banpai Manor.
Let me just go ahead and say it.
You're bananas.
Don't complain!
Mayonaka Punch
52k subscribers
Why?
Why aren't we gaining any subs?
All this hard work, for nothing?
We don't need that part!
Why not?!
We need to trim it down a little more.
Who was that?!
They're still awake?
Who stuffed green chilies in my nostrils?!
That should wake you up.
It's a good luck charm!
God, I swear!
Yeah!
The Outside Kids Anything Goes
Exposé Livestream Party!
About time we wrap things up, capisce?
Huh?!
You're really gonna end it like that?
That friggin' sucked!
Seriously, "capisce"?
They're really foul-mouthed...
And yet...
How despicable! Don't stop!
Hey, my loyal minions watching out there.
You'll tune in next time, right?
I will!
And of course you'll listen to our
new song dropping next week, right?
Of course!
All righty then!
Signing off, we're the Outside Kids!
And I'm an Outside Girl!
What's that mean?
Fu, that's what you're into? News to me.
Y-Y-You're mistaken!
I just, um, thought I could learn a lot
by watching some top streamers!
So, um, well... That is...
Why don't you come down?
You'll catch a cold.
Y-Yes.
Um, will you tell Live-sama and the others...
My lips are sealed.
That's a relief.
Have I been mistaken somehow all along?
Masaki-san?
Hey...
Are you subbed to the Outside Kids channel?
Y-Yes.
I gave them my very first.
Eh?
Okay, so why did you decide to subscribe?
W-W-W-Well...
Um, um, I mean, well...
Calm down.
Because those two were adorbs, perhaps.
Adorbs?
Yes.
So I wanted to watch more of them
and show my support.
That's why I subscribed.
Adorbs... Their blood...
Hey.
What exactly about them do you find "adorbs"?
That's, um...
Is it their gap?!
It is, right?!
You thought they were scary,
but they ended up being nice.
That's a part of it, sure.
But their relationship is what's adorbs.
Huh?
As they talk to each other,
it slips out sometimes.
Their true selves,
not the personas they've built!
The moment you get a peek, it's like...
Um...
I'm out of here!
Adorbs...
Adorbs.
When Hype-Sis blew up,
a lot of comments said the same thing.
Hyped-Up Sisters Z
325k subscribers
Latest             Popular            Oldest
It's Boba Time!!
Letting Loose with a Boba Party
Masakichi!
Kicchomu!
Otomin!
We are Hype-Sis—
Whoa, Masakichi's looks good!
Lemme try some!
You're right! Let me have some, too!
What? Let me think about it.
Huh? What's the big deal?
S-So young...
Hey!
Time for a sip!
Strawberry Milk
I think I'll also grab some boba tomorrow!
Rin
Gotta say... just adorbs <3
Satoru
I love hearing the three of you talk
Pudding Parfait
Really dig the laid-back vibes
Hedgehog Girl
Now I want some boba!
Eiko Fan
I've totally drank too fast and choked on
the pearls too lolol
Classic milk tea's fine but now I'm curious
about the mango one so I'll try it next time
Annie
You all get along so well~ I'm here for it.
It's Me Hana
So cute seeing Kicchomu always mess up,
Masakichi snark at her, and Otomin sitting
there with a smile. I could watch it all day.
yufu
literally laughed out loud around 7:40 lmao
It's Me Hana
So cute seeing Kicchomu always mess up,
Masakichi snark at her, and Otomin sitting
there with a smile. I could watch it all day.
yufu
literally laughed out loud around 7:40 lmao
nanami
i bet it's always a fun time with you three
Bury Me in Whipped Cream
Love that you're just a bunch of friends
who laugh at stupid stuff
Tangerine
I enjoyed getting a glimpse into the daily
lives of Hype-Sis!
Tangerine
I enjoyed getting a glimpse into the daily
lives of Hype-Sis!
Lemon Beer
Love that Kikka looks so stoic but acts
so dumb
Emperor Penguin
Girl on the left is cute.
anna
I was like "it's boba!" at the thumbnail,
and I wanted to watch while drinking some,
so I grabbed some by the station on my
way home!
Thrilling Chondroitin
This video's gonna go big... (who?)
anna
I was like "it's boba!" at the thumbnail,
and I wanted to watch while drinking some,
so I grabbed some by the station on my
way home!
Thrilling Chondroitin
This video's gonna go big... (who?)
Cocoa
10 min went by in a flash. Way too funny.
Pudding Parfait
You're such good friends, way too
adorbs!!!!!
Ankoro Mochi
I live in the middle of nowhere, so they
don't have boba places here ;w;
So jealous, must be nice.
I'll just have to make do with this video
instead.
macaron
macaron_OK
macaron_origdata1
macaron_trimmed
macaron_liveedit
Good morning from the dead of night!
Live here!
Ichiko!
Fu.
Tokage!
For today's video, we're under de-TEN-sion
until we eat all these giant macarons!
There are more than ten, though.
So picky!
Okay, let's dig in!
Taste Test
Oh!
Check out Fu drooling all over herself!
A-Am not!
Here I go!
So good!
How stupid.
Makeover!!
Total Wardrobe Change
for a Filthy Slob
Makeover!!
Total Wardrobe Change
for a Filthy Slob
Total Wardrobe Change for a Filthy Slob
A summer wardrobe for Tokage, our filthy slob!
Yay—
SHAWL
S-H-A-W-L...
Shawl
Shawl!
She turned out to like it <3
That looks great on you!
This is this year's—
I wanna try it on, too!
Tre—
Ichiko, these clothes
aren't for little kids to wear.
Trend—
I want to be element, too!
You mean "elegant."
Trend!
The Dessert Trending Now
Don't make a mess!
This one...
This Plain Jane
Can't Stop Talking About Fashion
And this one...
*LIVING IT UP* Spending Our Video Earnings on Trendy Items!!
860k views   2 weeks ago
And this...
Aw, man.
There! And over here... there!
No, that's wrong!
Then... like this?
That's it.
I-I did it!
You let your guard down.
A taste of your own wake-up call!
A maiden's nose is delicate!
Fu! Grab Tokage!
Eh?!
Stop, Tokage!
What?
Um...
I've realized something.
What?
The reason people subscribe to our channel...
It's your...
Huh?
It's your chemistry and your
true selves that they're into.
I thought I knew that already.
But I panicked all by myself about
trying to quickly gain subscribers.
And soon, I lost sight of everything.
I came up with strategies
based around gaps and trends,
but in the end, I was erasing
all of your best parts.
No wonder our channel wasn't growing.
Those so-called meaningless and pointless bits,
where you laughed, got angry, and worried
while getting along together as friends...
Those were MayoPan's strengths this whole time.
I'm always like this.
When I was with Hype-Sis,
I forged on ahead by myself
because we weren't growing
and ruined our friendship in the process.
It's no surprise that I ended up
getting kicked out.
I'm so stupid.
That's not—
So I'm sorry.
And that's why starting tomorrow—
There you go!
Panicking and going off all by yourself again!
I've said this before.
You've got me to help you now, don't you?
I'm here, too!
So you figured it out, right?
That's great!
Listen to me.
Starting now, let's all work together!
Instead of panicking by yourself,
we can all panic together!
And, well...
We tried editing this one more time as a group.
I put in all sorts of text!
You messed up a ton of kanji, though.
I-I handled the BGMs.
You were working on this the whole time?
We're still pretty bad at it.
Masaki, lean on us a little more from now on.
We'll be depending on you as well.
It's not MayoPan without all of us!
Got it?
I will.
In that case, without further ado...
Can we shoot a video?
And so, let's get started!
And so, what? Give us a rundown!
"Talking It Out in the Bath!"
Didn't I tell you?
What's important is your chemistry!
Forget about clothes, makeup,
ideas, and the camera,
and show us all your true selves!
I already took a bath.
You're totally doing this for the numbers!
Numbers are what we need!
Besides, Ichiko...
You'll be covered with an on-screen strawberry
from start to finish, so don't sweat it!
Why do you have to cover me up?!
So that our channel doesn't get banned!
I'm a hundred and ten!
Quiet!
You want to save Banpai Manor, don't you?
Give it up and pretend you're wearing
that strawberry costume you wanted!
C'mon!
Quit your yapping and let's get filming!
Okay! Ready, start!
Good morning from the dead of night!
Mayonaka Punch! Live here!
Today's video is "Talking It Out in the Bath!"
Hold on. We've been living
together for ages already.
There's nothing for us to talk about anymore.
I have a funny story for you
Oh, really?
Then I'll start...
I have something funny we can talk about.
Fu loves the Outside Kids!!
Wait—
Fu's a huge fan of the Outside Kids!
I've heard of them!
The NewTubers who wear shampoo hats!
Oh, is that why you love taking baths?
What do you see in that pair of phony,
empty-headed bell peppers, anyway?
D-Don't make fun of the Outside Kids!
Hell yeah!
Mayonaka Punch
101k subscribers
I guess everyone got a good
taste of MayoPan's chemistry!
Girls' Talk in the Bath
No way!
It's totally just because we were naked!
Are you really okay with such cheap tactics?!
Well, be that as it may, now we can
go back to one video per day.
Wait a second!
We should keep putting out three—
Masaki.
Well, you're right.
I want to shoot plenty of
your pointless moments.
The goal for step two was
100k subscribers, wasn't it?
So we can finally move on!
Yep.
Step three is...
Collabs with big names.
Collabs?
I took a long shot and sent out messages
to several people asking for a collab.
No way!
What's up?
An invitation to a NewTuber festival?
TSUMA-shi
To the members of Mayonaka Punch
Hello. My apologies for the
unsolicited message.
My name is TSUMA-shi,
and I post videos on NewTube.
I'm writing to you today to
discuss a business opportunity.
I will be hosting a NewTuber festival
event (TSUMA FES Extreme),
and currently, I'm reaching out
to a number of content creators to...
Fu
Sent you a sticker
Goodnight
Wh-Whoa! No way!
TSUMA-shi
Legendary streamer
known as the Stream God
TSUMA-shi himself?!
Masaki-san, you had a fave as well!
Oh, Fu!
Look, it's the Outside Kids!
What?!
But behind them is... TSUMA-shi in the flesh?!
Next time: "Starring in TSUMA FES Extreme!"
Starring in TSUMA FES Extreme!
I-I've got an extreme case of the nerves!